// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In order traversal of binary search tree will produce - ",
    answer: "Merge Sort",
    options: [
      "Merge Sort",
      "Insertion Sort",
      "Shell Sort",
      "Heap Sort"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What data structure is used for breadth first traversal of graph?",
    answer: "queue",
    options: [
      "stack",
      "queue",
      "list",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is an example for Dynamic programming approach?",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Fibonacci series",
      "Tower of hanoi",
      "Dijkstra Shortest Path",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Visiting root node after visiting left and right sub-trees is called ",
    answer: "Post-order Traversal",
    options: [
      "In-order Traversal",
      "Pre-order Traversal",
      "Post-order Traversal",
      "Middle-order Traversal"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following has search efficiency of 0(1)",
    answer: "Hash Table",
    options: [
      "Tree",
      "Heap",
      "Hash Table",
      "Linked List"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many swaps are required to sort the given array using bubble sort - {2,5,1,3,4}",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "5",
      "4",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Index of arrays in C programming language starts from ",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "either 0 or 1",
      "undefined"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "All possible spanning trees of graph G ",
    answer: "Have same number of edges and vertices",
    options: [
      "Have same number of edges and vertices",
      "Have same number of edges and but not vertices",
      "Not same ",
      "Depends on algorithm"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Shell sort uses ",
    answer: "insertion sort",
    options: [
      "insertion sort",
      "merge sort",
      "selection sort",
      "quick sort"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In conversion from prefix to postfix using stack data-structure, if operators and operands are pushed and popped exactly once, then the run-time complexity is ",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(log n)",
      "O(n2)"
    ]
  },

];